Guide to the Peter Safar Papers, 1950-2003 UA.90.F102
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Peter Safar Papers
1950-2003
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Safar, Peter
UA.90.F102
37.5 Linear Feet (30 boxes)
This collection contains the papers of Peter Safar, a distinguished professor of the University of Pittsburgh. The material includes correspondence between Safar and colleagues, meetings and conferences attended and created by Safar, organization and committee information, and copies of his publications. Also included are some of Safar's personal affects including awards given to Safar and his personal briefcase.
Previous Citation
Peter Safar Papers, 1950-2003, UA.90.F102, University of Pittsburgh Archives
Biography
Peter Safar was born into a family of medical professionals in Vienna, Austria, on April 12, 1924. He graduated from the University of Vienna in 1948 and a year later married his wife Eva while also moving to Hartford, Connecticut, to attend training at Yale University. In 1952 he trained at the University of Pennsylvania in Anesthesiology and in 1954 became Chief of Anesthesiology at Baltimore City Hospital, currently John Hopkins Bayview Medical Center. While there, he worked to create the ABCs of Cardio Pulmonary Resuscitation (CPR) which became the standard technique that was taught to medical professionals and lay people.
In 1961 he came to the University of Pittsburgh where he remained until his death in 2003. While in Pittsburgh he created many organizations to aid in critical care medicine, disaster medicine and the advancement of CPR. After the death of his daughter in 1966 Safar helped found the Freedom House Enterprise Ambulance Service, which provided one of the first services with trained Emergency Medical Technicians (EMT) to administer prehospital care. In 1979 he founded the International Resuscitation Research Center, currently the University of Pittsburgh Safar Center for Resuscitation Research, where he focused on Cardiopulmonary Cerebral Resuscitation (CPCR). Late in his career, Safar focused his research on reanimation.
Throughout his career, Safar received numerous awards. While at the University of Pittsburgh, he was awarded the honor of distinguished professorship for his contributions to the field of medicine, nationally and internationally. He was also given awards from the American Red Cross and became an honorary member of many foreign societies, like the Japan Society of Anesthesiology.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains the papers of Peter Safar, a distinguished professor at the University of Pittsburgh. Included is personal and professional correspondence between Safar and his colleagues, as well as material pertaining to Safar's participation in several conferences and organizations. The collection also contains many of Safar's published articles and manuals, as well as research files. The final series of this collection contains awards and information about Safar and his contribution to the world of medicine.
Access Restrictions
Access to files in Series I. Correspondence requires a signed Confidentiality Agreement due to the presence of incidental health care information.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Safar Center for Resuscitation Research in July 2014.
University of Pittsburgh; Faculty papers; CPR (First aid); Cardiopulmonary resuscitation; Resuscitation; Critical care medicine; Emergency medicine; Safar, Peter
- Correspondence, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series includes personal and professional correspondence between Peter Safar and his colleagues and associates, including fellows who were a part of the Safar Center. The series has been broken into five subseries and their organization has been maintained in their original order. Some of the correspondence within this series is written in languages other than English, including Spanish, German and Chinese. Additionally, access to the files in this series has been restricted due to the presence of personal identifiable or personal health information and require a signed confidentiality agreement to access.
  - Contacts, 1.
    This subseries includes correspondence between Peter Safar and colleagues. Much of this communication consists of Safar giving advice to others regarding the treatment of patients and the correct way to preform procedures. The records are arranged alphabetically by the correspondent's name and includes some restricted material.
    - Abouleish, Ezzat, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abrams, Joel, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Afanasiev, Vasily, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ahnefeld, Fritz, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Albright, A. Leland, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Alfonsi, Grace, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alifimoff, James, 1979-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alster, Howard, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Allon, Steven, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Artzner, Leon, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Aultman Fellow (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Aviado, Domingo M., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Baethmann, Alexander, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bagnato, Stephen J., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bakke, Frank, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bardoczky, Gizella, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Barnett, William Marc, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bednar, Stephen J., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Bellomo, Rinaldo, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Bentley, Timothy B., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Berden, H, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Berstad, Ketil, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Berzon, Jeffrey, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Betcher, Albert M., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bhafdwaj, Vidys B., 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bitterman, Haim, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Bok, Siegfried W., 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Boyd, David R., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Bradley, Keith, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Brandt, Allan A., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Breivik, Harold, 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Brinkmeyer, Scott, 1979-1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Brose, Richard, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Brown, Frank, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Burkhard-Meier, Caspar, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Butsch, Berthold, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Cadenas, Enrique, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Cain, James, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Carroll, Gilbert, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Caitlin, Rodger, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Chandler, John, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Chabal, Charles, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Cheever, Sarge, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Chodoff, Peter, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Chopp, Michael, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Clougherty, William (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Cochran, Jerome, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Comfort, Louise, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Comroe, Julius, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Conlay, Lydia (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Cordell, William, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Corssen, Guenter, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Couremenos, Stephanos, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Cotev, Shamay, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Cruel, Jan F., 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Custy, Jane C., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Cvachovec, Karel, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Damir, Elena, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Darbinyan, Tigran M., 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Darutzi, Albert (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Davies, James S., 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Davis, Raymond, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Dayton, Peter G., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Del Guercio, Louis, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Deneault, Lee, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Denny, Allen, 1975-1989 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Lanier, William, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Lechleuthner, Alex, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Lee, Chingmuh, 1980-1994 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Lee, Seung Kwon, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Lehndorff, Peter, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Leighninger, David S., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Leonov, Yuval, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Lesser, Raymond, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Lett, Zoltan, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Levey, Gerald S., 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Levey-Stickler Emergency Room Issue, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Levine, Robert Leslie, 1973-1994 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - L'Hommedieu, Todd, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Liu, Xiu-Wen, 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Llamosa, Jose Luis Bravo, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Leohning, Robert, 1962-1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Lovdal, Hans, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Luna, Manuel B., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lund, Ivar, 1978-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Lund, Ivar - Residents (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Macallister, Niall P., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Mackie, Ken, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - MacKrell, Tom, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - MacMurdo, Stanley D., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Marinov, Goran, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Marota, John (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Marsala, Josef, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Martin, Steve, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - McDonald, Robert H. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - McGlew, Mary Jo, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - McNulty, Patrick, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Menna, David, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Merikangas, James R., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Merin, Robert G., 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Meno, Frank, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Milhaud, Alvin, 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Miranda, Rodrigo, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Miro, Adelaida, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Morio, Michio, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Morse, Brad, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Mostert, Jacobus, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Mucci, Sam, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Mueller-Heubach, Eberhard, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Meyers, David P., 1979-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Myo, Khin Min, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Nakajo, Nobuyoshi, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Nelan, Graham, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Nishimura, Nobuo, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Nix, Wilfred, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Nord, Daniel, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Norton, Martin, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Noviant, Yvonne, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Paden, Susan, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Park, Gregory P., 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Peleska, Bohumil, 1963-1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Peleska, Bohumil, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Pilgeram Memorial Fund, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Puta, Ryszard, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Pontoppidan, Henning, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Poulsen, Henning, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Price, Henry L., 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Rainer, Helga, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Rao, M. Venkata, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Rapin, Maurice, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Ravi, Chaitanya Kumar, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Ratvitch, Mark, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Raynovich, William, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Regan, Raymond, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Reynoso, Samuel Quintana, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Rink-Ruff, Heldi, 1956-1975 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Rivas, Carlos, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Robotham, James, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Rogers, Robert, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Romoff, Jeffrey, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Rosborough, John, 1979-1989 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Saito, Reisuke, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Salek, Jeffrey S., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Salem, Mario, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Satin, Petko Dim, 1965-1973 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Schlobohm, Richard M., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Schneider, Glenn E, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Schneider, Sandra, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Scholten, Donald Jay, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Schwarzwaelder, Dietrich, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Schwentker, Ann, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Secher, Ole, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Sefrna, Bohumil, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Segall, Cornelia Iosif, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Shen, Bern, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Shirer, John, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Shubin, Hilde, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Shulman, Ivan, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Stevenpiper, Timothy S., 1973-1992 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Singer, Morley, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Singh, N.P., 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Smith, Ruth, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Snow, John C., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Shyngle, Joseph, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Solow, Victor, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Spence-Trembuhovich, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Spencer, Yvette, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Stadjuhar, Karl, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Stanko, Ronald Thomas (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Staub, Norman G., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Steinberg, Rob, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Stephan, Thorsten, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Stetson, John B., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Stewart, Charles, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Stewart, WIlliam D., 1963-1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Suter, Peter, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Syverd, Scott, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Tammisto, Tapani (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Taylor, Floyd H. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Tentschev, Peter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, Steve, 1975-1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Toennessen, Tor Inge, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Torpey, David, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Totten, Robert S., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Trimmer, Michael, 1976-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Ujike, Yoshihito, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Ulseth, Eirik, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ushijima, Kazuo, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Varga, Peter, 1961-1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Vienna CPR Research Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Vierira, Zairo, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Villanueva, Flordeliza (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Villar, Jesus, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Von Planta, Martin, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Vrana, Milan, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Vranova, Zdenka, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Fellows, 2.
    This subseries includes information on the fellows who were a part of the Safar Center. It is arranged alphabetically, contains some restricted material and also includes correspondence between Safar and the individual fellows.
    - Abraham, Alan, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Barr, Joseph, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Behringer, Wilhelm, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Eisenburger, Philip, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Hanson, Kristin R., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Holzer, Michael, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Kentner, Rainer, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Kentner, Rainer, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Khan, Lubna, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Nozari, Ala, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Nozari, Ala, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Pruekner, Stephan, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Yuichi, Sakai, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Woods, Randy, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wu, Xianren, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Wu, Xianren, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Professional Contacts, 3.
    This subseries includes correspondence between Peter Safar and the colleagues that were a part of his regular professional life. It is arranged alphabetically and includes some restricted material.
    - Bonaventura, Jiri, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bonica, John J., 1973-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bonica, John J. and Tom Hornbein, 1969-1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Borovetz, Harvey S., 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bozza-Marrubini, Marialuisa, 1988-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Brader, Eric, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Brader, Eric, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Brandom, Barbara, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Braslaw, Allan, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Braslaw, Allan, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Braslaw, Allan - CPR self-instruction video, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Braslaw, Allan - CPR Lay Paper, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Brindis, Charles, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Brouse, John S., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Brown, Mitch, 1976-1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Bruttig, Stephen P., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Buchman, Timothy G., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Buckman, Robert, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Buffington, Charles W., 1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Bircher, Nicholas, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bircher, Nicholas, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Birnbaum, Marvin, 1975-2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Bleyaert, Achiel, 1979-1991 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Blodi, Fredrick C., 1979-2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Boettiger, Bernd, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Boettiger, Bernd - Research Papers, 1994-1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Burkle, Fred, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Burkle, Fred - Disaster Medicine Chapters, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Callaway, Clif, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cantadore, Rinaldo, 1979-1988 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Canton, Angel, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Capone, Antonio, 1991-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Capone, Priscilla, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Carcillo, Joseph, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Caroline, Nancy L., 1968-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Caroline, Nancy L., 1985-1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Caroline, Nancy L., 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Caroline, Nancy L., 2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Carrillo, Peter, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Carter, Robert, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Cerchiari, Erga, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Cerchiari, Erga, 1986-2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Ceciliano, Norma, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Chandra, Nisha, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Clements, John, 1963-2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Coimbra, Cicero G., 2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Cook, Ryan, 1980-2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Coombs, MJ, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Cope, Doris, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Copeland, Charles E., 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Cowley, R. Adams, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cowley, R. Adams, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Crippen, David, 1982-1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Crippen, David, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Crippen, David, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Csete, Marie, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cummins, Richard, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Daehnick, Wilfried W., 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dahll, Hans, 1988-2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dandy, Walter, 1967-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Darby, Joseph, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Darwin, Michael, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Das, Niren, 1975-2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - DeAngelis, Catherine, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - DeKosky, Steven, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Delooz, Herman, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Detre, Katherine, 1977-2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Devita, Michael (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - DeWitt, Douglas, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Dick, Wolfgang, 1990-2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Diven, Warren, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Don Michael, T. Anthony, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Don Michael, T. Anthony, 1982-1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Doughty, Lesley, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Downes, John J., 1991-2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Drmanovic, Zoran, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Ebmeyer, Uwe, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Ebmeyer, Uwe, 1994-2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Fisher, Bernard, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Fisher, Bernard, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Foldes, Francis, 1970-2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Fredericks, Richard, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Freund, Michael, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Frey, Martin, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Frey, Rudolf, 1973-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Frey, Rudolf - Funeral, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Galla, Steven, 1966-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Galla Memorial Lectures, 1979-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Gamper, Martina, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Gazmuri, Raul J., 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Gelman, Barry, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Geocaidin, Romergyko, 1996-2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Georgieff, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Gilbertson, Lesley, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Ginsberg, Myron, 1990-2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Giroir, Brett, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Gisvold, Sven, 1978-1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Gisvold, Sven, 1990-2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Goldini, Claudio, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Goraieb, Sandra Miranda, 1992-2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Gorcsan, John, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Gordon, Archer, 1980-2003 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Steven, 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Gregory, George, 1976-1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Grenvik, Ake, 1979-1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Grenvik, Ake, 1989-1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Grenvik, Ake, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Grenvik Lectureship, 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Grenvik, Christer, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gruenbaum, Adolf, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Grundy, Betty, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Guanaes, Andre, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gunn, S. William, 1992-2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gurvitch, Alexander, 1978-1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hachimi-Idrissi, S., 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Halperin, Henry R., 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hardesty, Robert L., 1985-1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Hayashi, Nariuki, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Hayashi, Hoei (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Hedlund, Bo, 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Herberman, Ronald B., 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hickey, Robert, 1990-2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Hilberman, Mark, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hingson, Robert, 1948-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Hingson, Robert, 1980-1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Hingson, Robert, 1994-2003 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Hoel, Tor Martin, 1982-1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hofman, Klaus, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hohm, Wilhelm, 1991-2003 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Holland, Katherine, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Holzki, Josef, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Holzner, Burkhart, 1989-2003 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Homi, John, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Hosain, Syed, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Hossli, Georg, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hossman, Konstantin, 1975-1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Hoyt, John W., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Huber, Wolfgang, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Hugerth, Henry, 1997-2003 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Hurn, Patricia D., 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Idris, Ahamed H., 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Idrissi, Said, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - In Memoriam Articles (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Jannetta/Dandy Chairs, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Johns, Rodger, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Jordan, Mark, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Kagan, Valerian E., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Kai, Tatsuro, 1991-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Kameneva, Marina, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Kamm, Katrin, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Kampschulte, Marie Luise, 1993-2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Kampschulte, Stephen, 1966-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Kampschulte, Stephen, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Kampschulte, Stephen, 1994-2001 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Kanny, Mark, 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Kanter, Steven, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Kaplan-Labatova, Zuzana, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Kassil, Vladimir (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Katz, Laurence, 1982-1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Katz, Laurence, 1989-1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Katz, Laurence, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Katz, Laurence, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Kaye, William, 1978-1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Kelsey, Sheryl F., 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Kempen, Paul, 1977-1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)